(
"ai_sub_version": "2.5.0",
"lyrics_prompt_version": 2,
"subtitles_prompt_version": 12,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": null,
"model_subtitles": "gemini-cli:gemini-3-flash-preview",
"model_lyrics": "google-gla:gemini-3.1-flash-lite-preview",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"web_search_tool": "duckduckgo",
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true
),
"gemini_cli": (
"timeout": 600,
"overwrite_system_prompt": false
)
),
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": true,
"fps": 1,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"threshold_mb": 20,
"duration_tolerance_ms": 100,
"encoder": "libx264"
),
"start_offset_min": 0
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 2,
"lyrics": 4,
"subtitles": 4
),
"retry": (
"run": 3,
"max": 9,
"delay": 30
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": true,
"scrub": false
)
えー、皆様、本日は
Umm, everyone, today,
轟はじめ生誕祭2025にお越しくださいまして、
thank you very much for coming to
誠にありがとうございます。
Todoroki Hajime Birthday Celebration 2025.
開演に先立ちまして、
Prior to the start of the performance,
皆様にお願いとご案内を申し上げます。
I have some requests and information to share.
当配信は一部収録を含みますが、
This stream includes some pre-recorded parts,
生配信部分もございますので、
but there are also live stream parts,
いっぱいコメントして盛り上げてくだちゃい。
so please comment a lot and liven things up!
今も（コメント）見えてるんですけど...
I can see your comments now too...
ばんちょー！きゃー！ひーちゃー！おー！きゃー！
Bancho! Kyaa! Hi-cha! Oh! Kyaa!
えー、テレビやパソコン、スマートフォンの前での飲食は可能でしが、
Eating and drinking in front of your device is allowed,
キーボードにこぼさないよう、お気をつけください。
but please be careful not to spill on your keyboard.
当配信のハッシュタグは、「#轟はじめ生誕祭2025」でし。
The hashtag for this stream is "#TodorokiHajimeBirthdayCelebration2025".
SNSでたくさんポストしてくだちゃい。
Please post a lot on SNS.
開演中、パソコンやスマートフォンなどによる写真撮影、大歓迎でし。
Taking photos during the performance is more than welcome.
たくさんポストして盛り上げてくれると、うれちーでし。
I'll be happy if you post a lot and liven things up.
それでは、開演までしばらくお待ちくだちゃい。
Well then, please wait a while until the show starts.
うりゃー！皆様、本日は
Uryaa! Everyone, today,
轟はじめ生誕祭2025にお越しくださいまして、
thank you very much for coming to
誠にありがとうございます。
Todoroki Hajime Birthday Celebration 2025.
開演に先立ちまして、
Prior to the start of the performance,
皆様にお願いとご案内を申し上げます。
I have some requests and information to share.
当配信は一部収録を含みますが、
This stream includes some pre-recorded parts,
生配信部分もございますので、
but there are also live stream parts,
いっぱいコメントして盛り上げてくれると、すごくうれちーでし。
so I'll be very happy if you comment a lot.
じょわじょわ、2周目助かる、
Jowa-jowa, 2nd round helps,
わくわく、2回目。
waku-waku, 2nd time.
いいだろ2回言っても。ありがとね。
It's fine to say it twice, right? Thank you.
テレビやパソコン、スマートフォンの前での飲食は可能でしが、
Eating and drinking in front of your device is allowed,
キーボードにこぼさないよう、お気をつけください。
but please be careful not to spill on your keyboard.
当配信のハッシュタグは、「#轟はじめ生誕祭2025」でし。
The hashtag for this stream is "#TodorokiHajimeBirthdayCelebration2025".
SNSでたくさんポストしてくだちゃい。
Please post a lot on SNS.
開演中、パソコンやスマートフォンなどによる写真撮影も、大歓迎なので、
Taking photos during the performance is also very welcome,
いっぱいいっぱいいっぱいいっぱいポストしてくだちゃい。
so please post a lot, a lot, a lot, a lot!
それでは、開演までしばらく、もうちょっと、
Well then, for a little while, just a bit longer,
お待ちくだちゃい。
please wait for the show to start.
えっとなんだっけ
Um, what was it again?
謝っても無駄
It's no use apologizing
何がしたいか分からん
I don't know what you want to do
もううんざりだ
I'm fed up with this
馬鹿ばっかだ全く
Seriously, it's just a bunch of fools
あぁ 息苦しい世界だわ
Ah, what a suffocating world
1 2 3 からカウント
Counting from one, two, three
シャイなバッテン ゾンビに頼んだ
Asked the shy 'X' zombies
まやかしあやかしのズルビエ
The deceptive, haunting 'Zurubie'
天然物でスピタンザ
Natural-born 'Supitanza'
暴れる準備は決まって
The preparation to run wild is set
派手なイントロダクション唸った
A flashy introduction roared
夢のパーティーが始まりだ
The dream party is starting
あかんべのべ また べんべんべん
Sticking out my tongue, again, sticking it out
うるさい めんどくさあなも
Noisy, bothersome, everything
あいやいやいや
Ai yai yai ya
おっ あかんべのべ また べんべんべん
Oh, sticking out my tongue, again, sticking it out
懲りない 関わんなよ
Haven't learned your lesson? Don't get involved
だるいだけ
It's just tedious
揺れる 揺れる シンギング
Swaying, swaying, singing
圧倒的だな 宣誓
How overwhelming, this oath
まだまだ踊ってよ 御三唱
Keep on dancing, three cheers
揺れる 揺れる シンギング
Swaying, swaying, singing
圧倒的だな 宣誓
How overwhelming, this oath
清廉潔白 私の過去には 何の過ちもございません
Pure and innocent, my past has no mistakes
分厚くなってくルールブック 見逃した時には 万事休す
The rulebook thickens; if you miss a beat, all is lost
ビックリ精度のサーチライト
A searchlight with surprising precision
それはやばいよ が 一番怖いよ
Saying 'that's bad' is what's scariest
レッドもイエローも関係ないのよ
Red or yellow, it doesn't matter
一発退場！ はい！ お疲れさん！
Immediate ejection! Yes! Good work!
1 2 3 からカウント
Counting from one, two, three
熱いロックンロールを食らった
Struck by that hot rock 'n' roll
インターリュードに逆上せるビーナ
Getting dizzy on Venus during the interlude
バンギャのゾンビも バラバラ
Even the fan girl zombies are falling apart
アイドルタイムも終わって
Idol time is over too
あっちゅう間に こっから 終盤だぞ
In a flash, it's the final stage from here
ゾンビも猫も 三三五五
Zombies and cats, in small groups
あっち行ったり 来たり
Going here and there
あかんべのべ また べんべんべん
Sticking out my tongue, again, sticking it out
うるさい めんどくさあなも
Noisy, bothersome, everything
あいやいやいや
Ai yai yai ya
おっ あかんべのべ また べんべんべん
Oh, sticking out my tongue, again, sticking it out
懲りない 関わんなよ
Haven't learned your lesson? Don't get involved
だるいだけ
It's just tedious
揺れる 揺れる シンギング
Swaying, swaying, singing
圧倒的だな 宣誓
How overwhelming, this oath
まだまだ踊ってよ 御三唱
Keep on dancing, three cheers
揺れる 揺れる シンギング
Swaying, swaying, singing
圧倒的だな 宣誓
How overwhelming, this oath
まだまだ 割れるか？
Can we still break it down?
べん べん べん しないで
Stop sticking your tongue out
ラッタッタララ
Ra-ta-ta-ra-ra
なんだか せわしく笑う町
A town that somehow laughs busily
真夜中にバラバラ
Falling apart in the middle of the night
暴れてたゾンビとラグスタ
Zombies that ran wild and the 'Lag-star'
飛んでったシガレット
The cigarette that flew away
空から撃ち抜くバニーガール
A bunny girl shooting down from the sky
騒いでる様々
Various things making a noise
あらわれた近所のバランサー
The neighborhood balancer appeared
笑ったか緊張とスッサイド
Did you laugh? Tension and 'Southside'
この散状だって まだまだ行けるか
Even in this state, can we still go on?
ヘンドのチャイムが
The pendulum chime
想像通りじゃないなら
If this isn't how I imagined it
塗り替えてしまうのさ
I'll just paint it over
ゆらゆらゆらゆらどうぞ
Swaying, swaying, swaying, swaying, here you go
敗北とは 分かち合うものではないから
Defeat is not something to be shared
蹴っ飛ばし 染め上げてごらん
Kick it away and paint it over, see?
そんなもんさ
That's just how it is
ラッタッタッタッタラー
La ta ta ta ta ra
正直こんなの意味あるのかって
Honestly, I wondered if this had any meaning
考えたところで 堂々巡りで
And even if I thought about it, I'd just be going in circles
あれも これも それも 気になる 気になる 気になる
That, and this, and that, I'm curious, curious, curious
ラッタッタッタッタラー
La ta ta ta ta ra
それぞれに描いた正義が 絡み合う
The justices we each envisioned intertwine
あぁ まだまだ 行けそうだ
Ah, I can still keep going
ハッピーエンドのチャイムが
The happy end chime
想像通りじゃないなら
If this isn't how I imagined it
塗り替えてしまうのさ
I'll just paint it over
ゆらゆらゆらゆらどうぞ
Swaying, swaying, swaying, swaying, here you go
敗北とは 分かち合うものではないから
Defeat is not something to be shared
蹴っ飛ばし 染め上げてごらん
Kick it away and paint it over, see?
そんなもんさ
That's just how it is
ラッタッタッタッタラー
La ta ta ta ta ra
どこで何が起きるか分からない
I don't know what will happen where
またやり直せるかな
I wonder if I can start over again
ハッピーエンドのチャイムが
The happy end chime
想像通りじゃないなら
If this isn't how I imagined it
塗り替えてしまうのさ
I'll just paint it over
ゆらゆらゆらゆらどうぞ
Swaying, swaying, swaying, swaying, here you go
敗北とは 分かち合うものではないから
Defeat is not something to be shared
蹴っ飛ばし 染め上げてごらん
Kick it away and paint it over, see?
そんなもんさ
That's just how it is
ラッタッタッタッタラー
La ta ta ta ta ra
はい、ふぅ〜！
All right, phew!
皆さ〜ん！こんちこわ〜！
Everyone! Konchikowa!
初めての生誕祭、来てくれてありがとうございます！
Thank you for coming to my first birthday party!
＃タコは、轟はじめ生誕祭2025でしゅ！
Our hashtag is #TodorokiHajimeSeitansai2025!
たくさんポストしてくれたら嬉しいな〜！
I'd be happy if you post a lot!
トレンド入っちゃえ〜！
Let's make it trend!
ありがとうございます！嬉しい！
Thank you so much! I'm so happy!
今日は最高の色んなはじめをお届けするので、
Today, I'll be delivering all kinds of Hajime in the best way,
ぜひポストしてくれると嬉しいでしゅ！
so please do post about it!
先ほどは「神風」と「OFFSIDE」を聞いていただきました。
Earlier, you heard the songs 'Kamikaze' and 'OFFSIDE'.
どうでしゅか？
How were they?
カッコよかったでしゅか？
Were they cool?
ありがちょ、ありがちょ！
Thanks, thanks!
ありがちょね！
Thank you!
はじめはこの曲も、振り付けもめちゃくちゃ大好きなので、
I really love these songs and the choreography,
披露できて嬉しいでしゅ！
so I'm so happy I got to perform them!
この後もまだたくさんあるので、一緒に楽しんでください！
There's still more to come, so please enjoy them with me!
次は、今カッコよかったけど、
Next, they were cool just now, but...
ド派手なパーティーでしゅ！
it's a flashy party!
それでは、行きましょう！
Alright then, let's go!
Deal with the devil, yeah
興奮 たまらないわスリル
I can't get enough of the thrill
誰にも触らせない この money
I won't let anyone touch this money
Deal with the devil, yeah
愛さえ 金で買えるわ
Even love can be bought with money
Up down は世の常 崩し引いた札どうしない？
Ups and downs are common, what will you do with the cards you draw?
肝心なのは ストロングマインド 差し抜いて さぁ
The key is a strong mind, now draw your card
行き着く先は ヘブン or ヘル
The destination is heaven or hell
この世界のルール たった一つ 勝者こそが正義
Only one rule in this world, the winner is justice
女は度胸 散らさせるのよ あいつを
A woman needs guts, I'll make him fall apart
やれること何だってやる 私、賭ケグルイのクイーン
I'll do anything, I'm the Kakegurui Queen
Only straight you and me
読み切ってイカせてよ
Read through and make me win
全部さらけ出して見せて
Bare it all and show me
あたしのものにする あなたの髪の毛一本まで全部
I'll make it mine, every single strand of your hair
How million dollars you less?
How many million dollars you have less?
震えてるわよ 坊や
You're trembling, boy
降ろさせはしないわ
I won't let you fold
Deal with the devil, yeah 興奮 たまらないわスリル
Deal with the devil, yeah, I can't get enough of the thrill
誰にも触らせない この money
I won't let anyone touch this money
How million dollars you less?
How many million dollars you have less?
さぁ、賭けましょう
Now, let's gamble
覚悟決めて
Make up your mind
震え高ぶれ My heart
Tremble and soar, my heart
欲しがれ 容赦ねえ まだ Baby
Be greedy, show no mercy, more Baby
誰にも負けない 感じさせて Love me Honey
Let me feel I'll lose to no one, love me honey
あなたの正体は
Your true identity...
ほら 見せてあげる
look, I'll show you
秘密で甘いの
Something secret and sweet
仕掛けて罠にはめるわ
I'll set it up and trap you
油断誘うのよ
I'll lure you into lowering your guard
思考を止めたら The End
If you stop thinking, it's the end
何も知らないような
With a look as if you know nothing
顔で落とすわ 花束
I'll drop the flower bouquet with that face
寄せる 焦らすわ You're dummy
Come closer, I'll tease you, you're a dummy
読み切って連勝だ
Read you through, it's a winning streak
手出しは見逃さない
I won't miss a single move
どんな小さなズルだって
No matter how small the trick is
私の目は誤魔化されないわ
My eyes won't be deceived
1 million dollar 愛され
One million dollar, loved
勝って手に負えぬまで
Winning until I'm uncontrollable
愛し尽くしてあげる
I'll love you to the end
狙った獲物は
The prey I've aimed at
逃さない
I won't let it escape
唇 濡らして いただくわ My Babe
Wet your lips, I'll take it, my babe
新鮮感じてるわ
I'm feeling something fresh
望みは最後最高まで
My wish is to the very end
見てばかりいないで
Don't just watch
愛として行かない
Won't you go as love?
負けるのが怖い？
Afraid of losing?
弱いイジメ 読み切って連勝だ
Bullying the weak? I've read you through, it's a winning streak
手出しは見透かして
I see through your moves
私のものにする
I'll make you mine
あなたの髪の一本まで全部
Every single strand of your hair
1 million dollar 愛され
One million dollar, loved
震えてるわ 坊や
You're trembling, boy
どこまで行くわ
I'll go anywhere
手出しは 幸福
Every move is bliss
たまらないわ スリル
The thrill is irresistible
誰にも触らせない 黒目
I won't let anyone touch my eyes
1 million dollar 愛され
One million dollar, loved
さあ覚悟決めて
Now, make up your mind
灰になるまで打って
Hit it until it turns to ash
欲しがれ 容赦ねえ まだ Baby
Be greedy, show no mercy, more Baby
誰にも負けない 感じさせて Love me Honey
Let me feel I'll lose to no one, love me honey
丸ノ内サディスティック
Marunouchi Sadistic
作詞・作曲：椎名林檎
Lyrics/Composition: Sheena Ringo
報酬は入社後
The reward is after joining the company
並行線で
In parallel lines
東京は愛せど 何も無い
Though I love Tokyo, it has nothing
リッケン620頂戴
Give me a Rickenbacker 620
19万も持っていない
I don't even have 190,000 yen
御茶ノ水
Ochanomizu
マーシャルの匂いで
With the smell of a Marshall
飛んじゃって大変さ
I'm flying high, it's quite a thing
毎晩絶頂に
Every night, at the climax
達しているだけ
I'm just reaching it
ラット一つ
With just one ProCo Rat
商売道具にしているさ
I'm using it as my tool of the trade
そしたらベンジーが肺に写って
Then Benjie is reflected in my lungs
トリップ
And I'm tripping
報酬は入社後並行線で
The reward after joining is a parallel line.
東京は愛せど何にも無い
I love Tokyo, but there's nothing here.
リッケン620頂戴
Give me a Rickenbacker 620.
19万も持って居ない
I don't even have 190,000 yen.
御茶ノ水
Ochanomizu.
マーシャルの匂いで飛んじゃって大変さ
The smell of Marshall gives me a high.
毎晩絶頂に達して居るだけ
I'm just reaching a climax every night.
ラット1つを商売道具にしているさ
Using a single Rat as my tool of the trade.
将来僧になって結婚して欲しい
I want you to become a monk and marry me.
毎晩寝具で遊戯するだけ
I just play around in my bedding every night.
ピザ屋の彼女になってみたい
I want to try being the pizza guy's girlfriend.
そしたらベンジー、あたしをグレッチでぶって
Then, Benji, strike me with a Gretsch.
青噛んで行って頂戴
Please bite the blue and go.
終電で帰るってば池袋
I'm going home on the last train to Ikebukuro.
マーシャルの匂いで飛んじゃって大変さ
The smell of Marshall gives me a high.
毎晩絶頂に達して居るだけ
I'm just reaching a climax every night.
ラット1つを商売道具にしているさ
Using a single Rat as my tool of the trade.
そしたらベンジーが肺に写ってトリップ
Then Benji appears in my lungs and I trip.
将来僧になって結婚して欲しい
I want you to become a monk and marry me.
毎晩寝具で遊戯するだけ
I just play around in my bedding every night.
ピザ屋の彼女になってみたい
I want to try being the pizza guy's girlfriend.
そしたらベンジー、あたしをグレッチでぶって
Then, Benji, strike me with a Gretsch.
ありがとうございましたー！
次は『ツッパリHigh School Rock'n Roll』です！
Thank you so much!
Next is 'Tsuppari High School Rock'n Roll'!
今日も元気にドカンを決めたら
ヨーラン背負ってリーゼント
Rocking baggy pants with energy today,
school jacket on and a pompadour.
ツッパリHigh School Rock'n Roll
Tsuppari High School Rock'n Roll,
Tsuppari High School Rock'n Roll.
ソリも入れたし弁当も持ったし
Shaved my temples and brought my lunch.
可愛いあの娘はクルクルパーマに
長めのスカート引きずって
That cute girl has a curly perm
and drags her long skirt.
ツッパリHigh School Rock'n Roll
Tsuppari High School Rock'n Roll,
Tsuppari High School Rock'n Roll.
お手手つないで駅まで幸せ
Walking hand in hand to the station, so happy.
駅に着いたらドッペル兄ちゃんと
ガンのくれ合い飛ばし合い
At the station, trading glares
and shouting with a scary guy.
ツッパリHigh School Rock'n Roll
Tsuppari High School Rock'n Roll,
Tsuppari High School Rock'n Roll.
タイマンはりましょ 赤テープ同士で
Let's have a duel, red-tape buddies.
母ちゃん、そんな心配すんなよ
Mom, don't worry so much.
勉強嫌いな俺らだけどさ
We hate studying, but...
人にはそれぞれあった道ってもんがあんねん
everyone has a path that suits them.
もっと大きな愛で、今の俺を包んで欲しいな
I want you to wrap me in a bigger love.
おいお前！あそこにまぶい女がいるじゃんよ！
Hey you! There's a babe over there!
どっちも男連れてんな
They're both with guys.
おら、やるんじゃねえ！
Hey, don't do that!
電車に乗ったら便所に駆け込み
一駅だけのハッピータイム
Rush to the toilet on the train,
a one-station happy time.
ツッパリHigh School Rock'n Roll
Tsuppari High School Rock'n Roll,
Tsuppari High School Rock'n Roll.
火のないところに煙を立てて
Making smoke where there's no fire.
電車を飛び降り改札抜けたら
学校まではもうダッシュ
Jump off the train and through the gate,
then dash to school.
ツッパリHigh School Rock'n Roll
Tsuppari High School Rock'n Roll,
Tsuppari High School Rock'n Roll.
またまた遅刻で今日も呼び出し
Late again, called in today too.
Thank you! 来てくれてありがとう！
Thank you! Thanks for coming!
バレる！
Exposed!
Oh yeah ちょっと待て 何これ 知らぬ間に変わり果て
Oh yeah, wait a second, what's this? Changed completely...
Oh yeah どこにも見当たらない人の足跡
Oh yeah, footprints of people nowhere to be found.
胸の高鳴り抑え 送り込む肺に酸素
Suppressing the thumping of my heart, oxygen to lungs,
また増え 灰色の惨状 荒野の百鬼夜行
increasing again, gray tragedy, a demon night parade.
Who's next 次は誰が吐き出す画期的な自画像
Who's next? Who'll spit out a revolutionary self-portrait?
数千の屍かき分け誰もが血眼
Pushing through thousands of corpses, all bloodshot eyes.
上も下もパンパンな末期的症状
Up and down, it's packed, terminal symptoms.
前後不覚 現れ見せつける徳と飢えた力を
Unconscious of everything, showing virtue and hunger.
辿り着いたあの追い風 邪魔ならそこどいとけ
Reached that tailwind, if you're in the way, move aside.
白線の内側へ Hundred percent 練馬の呼び声
Inside the white line, 100%, the call of Nerima.
Oh yeah えげつないもん発明したのかもな
Oh yeah, maybe I invented something nasty.
生中継 革命前夜 歓声下のラボ
Live broadcast, eve of revolution, lab under cheers.
バレる はぁ？ この俺の天賦の才がバレる
Exposed! Huh? My natural talent's getting exposed!
マジこれ面倒くさいな バレる
Seriously, this is a pain, exposed!
はぁ？ バレる 世の中に気付かれる
Huh? Exposed! Noticed by the world.
Let's get it 追い風 駆けろ Oh my haters
Let's get it, tailwind, run! Oh my haters!
とりあえずはヴィランでしょ
For now, you're the villain, right?
ほら見たことか ニヤけろ
See? I told you so. Go ahead and grin.
Oh yeah 拍手と歓声 ここ日の当たる場所
Oh yeah, applause and cheers, here in the sunny spot.
沈着冷静 地に足つけたままありがとう
Calm and composed, feet on the ground, thank you.
地名も名声も水物 活版所の箱
Fame is fleeting, just boxes in the printing shop.
頭でわかっちゃいるくせに 体が麻痺してくミステリー
I know it in my head, yet my body's paralyzed mystery.
吐き出す ここに唸るサビ 息も漏らさぬイス取りゲーム
Chorus roaring here, musical chairs with no breath.
1度のミス 買い主なし 誰の手のひら返し一斉に
One mistake, no buyer, everyone turns at once.
白黒つけられない もう捨て身じゃいられない
Can't tell black from white, no longer desperate.
やばい 失うものが欲しい 欲しい 欲しい 欲しい
Bad, I want something to lose, want it, want it!
俺をわかってくれと叫び 世に知らしめたばかりに
Cried out for understanding, just to make a name.
自分で自分をより自分らしく演じなきゃいけないハメに
Now I'm stuck acting more like myself than ever.
求められてるあのアジでも 俺はもうそこにはいない
Even with that taste they want, I'm not there anymore.
俺って誰？ 俺って何？ ビビって手も足も出ない
Who am I? What am I? Scared stiff.
バレる はぁ？ 俺にはもう何にもないや バレる
Exposed! Huh? I have nothing left, exposed!
はぁ？ やっぱ端から勘違いだった バレる
Huh? It was a misunderstanding from the start, exposed!
はぁ？ バレる 化けの皮剥がされる
Huh? Exposed! The mask is being stripped off.
Let's get it 追い風 駆けろ Oh my haters
Let's get it, tailwind, run! Oh my haters!
手を叩いて 指差して
Clapping hands, pointing fingers.
ほら見たことか 笑える
See? I told you so. It's laughable.
生きてる限りは勝ち逃げできねぇな
As long as I'm alive, I can't just win and run.
衰え錆びつき同化されてしまう定めか
Destined to fade, rust, and be assimilated?
メッキを剥いだのは 熱病を描いたのは
Stripping the plating, depicting the fever...
あの日の俺とよく似た目をした奴でした
was someone with eyes just like mine that day.
あいにく俺はまだ三途の川
Unfortunately, I'm still at the Sanzu River.
今日もまた積み上げては蹴り飛ばされる賽の河原
Stacking stones only to have them kicked away.
痛みも飽きた ニヤリと微笑んだ
Tired of the pain, I grinned.
ジッと殺し伸ばす刀と 後を引く死に体
Staring, sword ready, a lingering dying body.
バレる はぁ？ この俺の天賦の才がバレる
Exposed! Huh? My natural talent's getting exposed!
マジこれ面倒くさいな バレる
Seriously, this is a pain, exposed!
はぁ？ バレる 世の中に気付かれる
Huh? Exposed! Noticed by the world.
Let's get it 追い風 駆けろ Oh my haters
Let's get it, tailwind, run! Oh my haters!
とりあえずはヴィランでしょ
For now, you're the villain, right?
ほら見たことか ニヤけろ
See? I told you so. Go ahead and grin.
ぺちゃ、ありがとー！
Pecha, thank you!
ありがとー！
Thank you!
助かる
That helps.
こんちくわ
Kon-chikuwa
轟はじめ
Todoroki Hajime
こん！
Kon!
ちくわ！
Chikuwa!
こん！こん！ちくわ！
Kon! Kon! Chikuwa!
こん！
Kon!
ちくわ！
Chikuwa!
ぶんぶんぶん
Bun bun bun
こん！ちくわ！
Kon! Chikuwa!
こん！こん！ちくわ！
Kon! Kon! Chikuwa!
こん！
Kon!
ちくわ！
Chikuwa!
ちくわ！ちくわ！
Chikuwa! Chikuwa!
おっ
Oh
おっおっおっふーん
Oh, oh, oh, hmm
泣いちゃうぞ ぴえんぴえん
I'm gonna cry, pien pien
おっおっおっすごーい
Oh, oh, oh, amazing
うーん すきっ
Hmm, love it
おっおっおっおっ
Oh, oh, oh, oh
泣いちゃうぞ ぴえんぴえん 泣いちゃうぞ
I'm gonna cry, pien pien, I'm gonna cry
泣いちゃうぞ
I'm gonna cry
ごみゃん
Gomyan
こん！ちくわ！ こん！こん！ちくわ！
Kon! Chikuwa! Kon! Kon! Chikuwa!
こん！ちくわ！
Kon! Chikuwa!
最終手段抱いてやる
Last resort, I'll embrace you
こん！ちくわ！ こん！
Kon! Chikuwa! Kon!
こんちくわ！ こんちくわ！ ちくわ！
Kon-chikuwa! Kon-chikuwa! Chikuwa!
こん！こん！ こん！こんちくわ！
Kon! Kon! Kon! Kon-chikuwa!
ぴゃ！ぴゃ！ぴゃ！ぴゃ！
Pya! Pya! Pya! Pya!
あい！あい！げんき！あい！
Ai! Ai! Energetic! Ai!
カッツォでき仮想敵？カッツォでき仮想敵？
Katsuo can hypothetical enemy?
あー仮想敵か
Ah, hypothetical enemy, huh
ぴゃ！ぴゃ！ぴゃ！ぴゃ？
Pya! Pya! Pya! Pya?
あい！あい！げんき！あい！
Ai! Ai! Energetic! Ai!
泣かれたら泣き返す
If you cry, I'll cry back
今を生きるよ！
Living in the moment!
やさしいじゃん えー抱くかあ
That's kind. Well, shall I embrace you?
こん！ちくわ！ こん！こんちくわ！ こんちくわ！
Kon! Chikuwa! Kon! Kon-chikuwa! Kon-chikuwa!
こん！こん！ こーん！ こん！こんちくわ！
Kon! Kon! Koon! Kon! Kon-chikuwa!
こんちくわ！
Kon-chikuwa!
こん！ちくわ！ こん！
Kon! Chikuwa! Kon!
ちくわ！ こん！ ちくわ！
Chikuwa! Kon! Chikuwa!
おわり！
The end!
わぁー！
Wow!
あのー ノエル先輩がね
So, Noel-senpai...
ラップしてたんだよー ちょっと対抗してみようかな
was rapping. I thought I'd try to compete a bit.
もちょっと 韻踏めない気がするけど
I don't think I can rhyme very well, though.
もう頭まわんなくて
My head isn't working anymore.
よし これで行こう！
Alright, let's go with this!
ふちゅかめ！
Second day!
ノエル団ちょーに対抗！
Going up against Captain Noel!
うちがらっぱんちょー！
I'm the Rap Bancho!
ラップでバトルしよーよー！
Let's have a rap battle!
うちがらっぱんちょー！
I'm the Rap Bancho!
初テイムはぶんぶんてんちょー
My first tame was Bunbun Manager
初レイドであっけなく終了！
The first raid ended in an instant!
その次テイムしたのは アルゲンなんだよー！
The next one I tamed was an Argent!
トワさんとフブキさんで
With Towa-san and Fubuki-san...
大冒険なYO！
...it's a big adventure!
ビーバーとっこら！ セメント大量！
Beaver charge! Lots of cementing paste!
大成功でおわったYO！
It ended in a huge success!
もっと強くなるばんちょー！
Bancho will get even stronger!
おい、ノエル！ お前負けてんぞ！
Hey, Noel! You're losing!
時間なさすぎてラップできなかった未熟者だよ！
I'm just a novice who didn't have time to rap!
おい、やばい。やめてよ！
Wait, this is bad. Stop it!
日記でラップバトル始めないでよ！
Don't start a rap battle in your diary!
全然いいけど！ ラップバトルしよーね！
It's fine, but let's have a proper rap battle!
ふちゅかめ！ 二日目！
Second day! Second day!
ノエル団ちょーに対抗！
Going up against Captain Noel!
うちがらっぱんちょー！
I'm the Rap Bancho!
ラップでバトルしよーよー！
Let's have a rap battle!
うちがらっぱんちょー！
I'm the Rap Bancho!
初テイムはぶんぶんてんちょー
My first tame was Bunbun Manager
初レイドであっけなく終了！
The first raid ended in an instant!
その次テイムしたのは アルゲンなんだよー！
The next one I tamed was an Argent!
トワさんとフブキさんで 大冒険なYO！
With Towa and Fubuki, it's a big adventure!
ビーバーとっこら！ セメント大量！
Beaver charge! Lots of cementing paste!
大成功でおわったYO！
It ended in a huge success!
もっと強くなるばんちょー！
Bancho will get even stronger!
番長の勝利 おめでとう！
Bancho wins! Congratulations!
I'm Koseki Bijou!
アイム 轟はじめ！
I'm Todoroki Hajime!
Boom Boom Boom!
はじめまして！
Nice to meet you!
いっしょに うたおー！ Let's go!
Let's sing together! Let's go!
Cool? Yeah! Thank you, thank you.
アイム ばんちょー Yeah Bancho yeah
I'm Bancho yeah, Bancho yeah
We were cool, right?
あーくーる おーけー？
Are cool okay?
ベリベリハッピー Very very happy
Very very happy, very very happy
Can you say something for me?
Sticking out your gyatt for Nerizzler!
なに、なに、なに！？
Wait, what what what!?
You're so Bau bau!
You're so Biboo tax!
I just wanna be your Shiori!
Yeay! She said the thing!
STICKING OUT YOUR GYATT FOR NERIZZLER
YOU'RE SO BAU BAU
YOU'RE SO BIBOO TAX
I JUST WANNA BE YOUR SHIORI
This one! Wow wow wow! Are you ready?
Cool? Yeah! Thank you, thank you.
アイム ばんちょー Yeah Bancho yeah
I'm Bancho yeah, Bancho yeah
We were cool, right?
あーくーる おーけー？
Are cool okay?
ベリベリハッピー Very very happy
Very very happy, very very happy
I want to hear the word "Bijou senpai's Ryourya".
りょうりゃ
Ryourya
はい？？
Excuse me??
聴いてー 聴いてーよもう
Listen, listen to me already!
ぽろぽろ
Poro poro
いまフワモコがばんちょー先生のところに向かってます！
Fuwamoko is heading to Bancho-sensei right now!
オーバー！
Over!
ばんちょーせんせー はじめ
Bancho-sensei Hajime
ばんちょー先生、いま持ってます！
Bancho-sensei, I'm holding you now!
持たれてます
I'm being held
次はちょっとつめたいよ
Next is a little cold
つめたーい！ がまんしてねー！
It's cold! Please bear with it!
わ！ つめたい！
Whoa! It's cold!
おへそにつめたーい！
It's cold on my belly button!
OK じゃあ
OK then
次はハートマッサージね
Next is a heart massage
ハートマッサージ？ マッサージ！
Heart massage? Massage!
BAU BAU BAU BAU...
大丈夫！ 大丈夫！
It's okay! It's okay!
信じてるよ！
I believe in you!
I believe you!
パワー！
Power!
BAU BAU BAU...
ソーセージ！
Sausage!
お腹が痛いよー
My stomach hurts...
全部大丈夫になるからね BAU BAU
Everything will be okay, BAU BAU
これで大丈夫かなー！ げんきになった！
I wonder if this is okay! I'm all better!
これからも病院がんばろー！
Let's keep doing our best at the hospital!
うん、がんばろーね！ BAU BAU！
Yeah, let's do our best! BAU BAU!
殴り合いますか？
Shall we trade blows?
あ、殴り合う？ いいよ。
Oh, trade blows? Sure.
ちょっといま、溜まってるわ。
I've got some built-up stress right now.
溜まってるw やめてw
Built-up stress? lol Stop it lol
まあ久々にやるからね。
Well, it's been a while.
ちょっ、できるか。
Wait, can I even do this?
イクゾッ！
Here I go!
負けねぇ！ 負けねぇ！ やめろー！
I won't lose! I won't lose! Stop it!
勝つ！ やめてー！
Win! Stop it!
イヤー！
Eek!
ドワーデイ ドゥォーオー
Dwa-dei Dwo-oo
キョーオー ドワーデイ ドゥォーオー
Kyo-oo Dwa-dei Dwo-oo
チョフィチョフィ ヤーー！
Chofichofi Yaaa!
おれの勝ち
I win
完全勝利
Complete victory
ボール持って モチュッ
Hold the ball, Mochu
ピュイ〜 ホイッ
Pyui~ Hoi!
チョイチョイチョイチョイ
Choi choi choi choi
ピュイ〜 えいっ えいっ
Pyui~ Ei! Ei!
ボール持って モチュッ
Hold the ball, Mochu
あいゃ あいゃ ホイッ
Aiya aiya Hoi!
Yes, I do.
ぶんぶんぶーん ばんちょー
Vroom vroom, Bancho
あ ぶんぶんぶんぶーん あめめめめめみゃー
Ah vroom vroom, amememememya!
轟はじめです
I'm Hajime Todoroki
またの名を ただの甘えん坊だ
Also known as just a spoiled child
白銀ノエル
Noel Shirogane
またの名を 牛丼太郎だ
Also known as Gyudon Taro
よろしくな
Nice to meet you
おれの勝ち
I win
完全勝利
Complete victory
なんなんだ このゲーム
What even is this game?
まあ キャーキャーじゃどうにもならんかったか
Well, screaming didn't help at all
どうも もるでちおです
Hello, I'm Morudechio
でび様に負けたので
Since I lost to Debi-sama...
今からでび様考案の うんちぷりぷりだんすをします
I'll now do the Poo-Poo Dance created by Debi-sama
うんちゃ ぷりゃぷりゃ... うんちゃ
Un-cha purya-purya... Un-cha
異界の扉 開かれ中 から来た
Came from the opened gate of another world
轟はじめ またの名を
Hajime Todoroki, also known as...
はじめ はじめ はじめ よろしく
Hajime, Hajime, Hajime, nice to meet you
悪魔中から来た でびでび・でびる
Came from within the devil, Debi Debi Debiru
またの名を うんちうんちうんち
Also known as Poo Poo Poo
うんち うんち... うんち王
Poo poo... Poo King
はじめまして
Nice to meet you
ありがたきできてくださって
Thank you so much for coming
じゃあ今度は僕が 踊ってって言ったら 踊ってくれる？
So next, if I say "dance", will you dance?
うんちぷりぷりダンス
Poo Poo Dance
うんちゃ ぷりゃぷりゃ... うんちゃ
Un-cha purya-purya... Un-cha
またね
See you
また遊んでください
Please play with me again
やったー！
Yay!
せーのっ
Ready, go!
おつもるでちおー
Otsu-morudechio!
わあ、すごい楽しいコラボだったでございます
Wow, that was such a fun collab!
おいで、はじめちゃん、こっちこっち
Come here, Hajime-chan, over here!
いや、すごい楽しかったでございます
Man, that really was a lot of fun!
あとトレンドも1位に入ったという ことなんですかね？ありがとうございます！
And we hit #1 on trending? Thank you so much!
豪華10名のゲストが来てくださいました。嬉しいあ。
Ten amazing guests joined us. I'm so happy!
おだまよ先生のこれまでの作品をメドレーにしてもらいました。
We had a medley made of Odamayo-sensei's works.
可愛いメドレーありがとうございます。ぜひいろいろ見てください。
Thanks for the cute medley. Everyone, check them out!
本当に先輩も同期も皆来てくれて、本当に嬉しい。またコラボしてほしいな。
I'm so glad everyone came. I hope we can collab again!
はい、ということでね、えー、皆さん、どうでちたか？
Anyway, everyone, how was it?
おちんちこじんって言うな。いつも通り可愛いだろう？
Don't call me that. I'm cute as always, right?
これからまたダンスを披露したいので、ストレッチしてくるわ。
I'm going to stretch so I can perform another dance.
ちょっと待ってて。
Wait a moment.
ボキボキ、うわ、ちょっと体固くなってたわ。伸びた伸びた。
Crack... my body was stiff. All stretched out now!
ということでね、次の曲行きたいと思います。
Alright, let's move on to the next song.
聴いてください、ワールドイズマイン。
Please listen: World is Mine.
世界で一番おひめさま
The number one princess in the world
そう　ずっと　熱い　鼓動へ
Yes, forever, towards the hot heartbeat...
いっくよー！
Here we go!
その一　いつもと違う髪形に気がつくこと
Number one: Notice when I have a different hairstyle.
その二　ちゃんと靴まで見ること　いいな？
Number two: Look properly down to my shoes, okay?
その三　私の一言には三つの言葉で返事すること
Number three: Reply to my every word with three words.
わかったら右手がお留守なのをなんとかして！
If you understand, do something about my empty right hand!
別にわがままなんて言ってないんだから
It's not like I'm being selfish or anything,
キミに心から思って欲しいの　かわいいって
I just want you to think I'm cute from your heart.
世界で一番おひめさま
The number one princess in the world,
気がついて　ねえねえ
Notice me, hey, hey.
待たせるなんて論外よ
Keeping me waiting is out of the question.
私を誰だと思ってるの？
Who do you think I am?
もう何だか　甘いものが食べたい！
I feel like... I want to eat something sweet!
今すぐに　よ
Right now.
Check one two!
欠点？かわいいの間違いでしょ
Flaws? You must mean 'cute' instead.
文句は許しませんの
I won't allow any complaints.
あのね、私の話ちゃんと聞いてる？ちょっと...
Hey, are you listening to what I'm saying? Hey...
あ、それとね　白いお馬さん　決まってるでしょ？
Oh, and another thing: a white horse, it's a given, right?
迎えに来て
Come and pick me up.
わかったら　かしずいて手を取って「おひめさま」って
If you understand, kneel, take my hand, and call me 'Princess'.
別にわがままなんて言ってないんだから
It's not like I'm being selfish or anything,
でもね　少しくらい叱ってくれたっていいのよ？
But you know, it's okay if you scold me just a little bit?
世界で私だけのおうじさま
The only prince in the world for me,
気がついて　ほらほら
Notice me, look, look.
おててが空いてます
My hand is empty.
無口で無愛想なおうじさま
My quiet and blunt prince,
もう　どうして！
Jeez, why?!
気がついてよ早く
Notice me already!
ぜったいキミはわかってない！
You definitely don't get it!
わかってない...
You don't get it...
いちごの乗ったショートケーキ
Shortcake with strawberries on top,
こだわり卵の　とろけるプリン
Melting pudding made with special eggs...
みんな　みんな　我慢します...
I'll endure it all, all of it...
わがままな子だと思わないで
Don't think of me as a selfish girl,
私だってやればできるもん
I can do it if I try,
あとで後悔するわよ
You'll regret it later.
当然です！だって私は
Of course! Because I am...
世界で一番おひめさま
The number one princess in the world,
ちゃんと見ててよね
Keep your eyes on me,
どこかに行っちゃうよ？
Or I'll go somewhere else, okay?
ふいに抱きしめられた
Suddenly, you hugged me.
急に　そんな　えっ？
All of a sudden... like that... what?
「轢かれる、危ないよ」
"You'll get run over, it's dangerous,"
そう言ってそっぽ向くキミ
You said, looking away.
...こっちのが危ないわよ
...this is more dangerous.
街の明かりが滲んでる
The city lights are blurring,
そっと　手で　触れそうな三日月
The crescent moon that seems touchable softly by hand.
あなたに会える...
I can meet you...
特別な日はハッピー
Special days are happy
さっき
Just now
きらめくダイヤモンドで
With a sparkling diamond
いつもよりゆっくり
Slower than usual
いつもよりも早く
Faster than usual
一緒にいたくて
I wanted to be with you
慣れないハイヒール
High heels I'm not used to
よろめいちゃうから
Because I'll stumble
腕を貸してそんなの
Lend me your arm, things like that
見え見えかしら
Is it too obvious?
恋はイリュージョン
Love is an illusion
すこしロマンティック
A bit romantic
予想できない
Unpredictable,
取り乱させて
making me lose my cool
恋はイリュージョン
Love is an illusion
すこしファンタスティック
A bit fantastic
隠しきれない
Can't hide it,
この胸のドキドキ
this heart's pounding
瞳閉じてみたら
If I try closing my eyes
シュワシュワシュワシュワ
Fizzing and bubbling
聞こえてくるでしょ
You can hear it, right?
映画のワンシーンみたいに
Like a scene from a movie
キュンとする
My heart skips a beat
仕草リサーチしてみても
Even if I research gestures
あなたに会った瞬間全部
The moment I meet you, everything...
あいまい揺れてるピンクサファイア
...becomes vague, a swaying pink sapphire
言葉よりめちゃめちゃ
More than words, so much more
めちゃめちゃより心で
More than "so much", with my heart
通じ合ってたいの
I want to be in tune with you
慣れない静けさに
In the unfamiliar silence
緊張しちゃうから
Because I get nervous
微笑んでねそんなの
Please smile at me, things like that
贅沢かしら
Is it too selfish?
恋はイリュージョン
Love is an illusion
甘いテンプテーション
Sweet temptation
予想できない
Unpredictable,
取り乱させて
making me lose my cool
恋はイリュージョン
Love is an illusion
甘いテンプテーション
Sweet temptation
隠しきれない
Can't hide it,
この胸のドキドキ
this heart's pounding
シャンパンの泡のよう
Like champagne bubbles
シュワシュワシュワシュワ
Fizzing and bubbling
弾けているでしょ
They're popping, right?
恋はイリュージョン
Love is an illusion
すこしロマンティック
A bit romantic
予想できない
Unpredictable,
ふとした温もり
a sudden warmth
恋はイリュージョン
Love is an illusion
かなりファンタスティック
Quite fantastic
隠しきれない
Can't hide it,
この胸のドキドキ
this heart's pounding
瞳閉じてみたら
If I try closing my eyes
シュワシュワシュワシュワ
Fizzing and bubbling
聞こえてくるでしょ
You can hear it, right?
いつまで子供のままでいる？
How long will you stay a child?
そんな言葉が降りかかる
Those words rain down on me
黙って見ていればいいんだ
You should just watch in silence
笑ってそう言ってやれ
Smile and tell them that
人生にはないんだ take 2
There's no take 2 in life
平凡でくだらない退屈
Commonplace, worthless boredom
なんてごめんだ 現実的な
No thank you to that; to realistic...
言葉なんかに耳をふさぎ
...words, I'll block my ears
ネバーランドに閉じこもって
Shutting myself away in Neverland
いつまでだって夢を語るんだ
I'll talk about my dreams forever
笑う奴には唾を吐け
Spit on those who laugh
にっちもさっちもいかない
Getting stuck in a bind
綺麗事に踊り躍らされ
Dancing to empty platitudes
大人の言う常識なんてものは
The common sense adults talk about...
丸めて捨てちまえ
...roll it up and throw it away
ピーターパン症候群と
Even if I'm called a Peter Pan syndrome...
指をさされて罵られようが
...and pointed at and insulted
おとぎ話みたいなハッピーエンドを
A fairy-tale happy ending...
思い描いて生きていくんだ
...I'll keep envisioning as I live on
Wow...
こっち指差して笑ってんだろ
You're pointing here and laughing, aren't you?
好きに笑えよ それで別にいいさ
Laugh all you want, I don't really mind.
お前なんかに そう お前らなんかに
By someone like you... yeah, by people like you...
なにも言われたくない 黙って見てろ
I don't want to be told anything. Just sit back and watch.
やり直しのきかない人生 一度でいいチャンスをください
In this life with no do-overs, just give me one chance.
掴んで離さない もう俺のものなんだ
I'll grab it and never let go. It's mine now.
ネバーランドの 大気圏を破って今 夢を叶えんだ
Breaking through Neverland's atmosphere, I'll fulfill my dream now.
笑う奴など 蹴り飛ばせ
Those who laugh... I'll just kick them away.
打つ手はない残されてない？ ネガティブを押し付けてくんな
"No more moves left?" Don't force your negativity on me.
大人のあいつらも知らない世界を 俺は生きてるんだ
I'm living in a world even those adults don't know.
ピーターパン症候群と 思われたって馬鹿にされたって
Even if they think it's Peter Pan Syndrome or mock me,
おとぎ話みたいなハッピーエンドに 一直線に進んでいくんだ
I'll head straight for a fairy-tale happy ending.
夢の見過ぎと馬鹿にされた少年が 夢を掴む物語を
The story of a boy mocked for dreaming too much, seizing his dream...
見事な逆転劇を この手で巻き起こせ
I'll cause a brilliant reversal with these hands.
見せつけろ
Show them what you've got!
にっちもさっちもいかないよ 綺麗事に踊り踊らされ
Trapped in a stalemate, dancing to empty platitudes...
大人の言う常識なんてものは 丸めて捨てちまえ
Take that "common sense" adults talk about and throw it away.
ピーターパン症候群と 指をさされ罵られようが
Even if they point fingers and call it Peter Pan Syndrome,
おとぎ話みたいなハッピーエンドを 自ら掴み取るんだ
I'll grab that fairy-tale happy ending for myself.
はい！
Yes!
えー、こんはじめ、轟はじめです。
Um, Kon-hajime! I'm Todoroki Hajime.
初めてタップに挑戦しました。声は入るでしょうか？
I tried tap dancing for the first time. Can you hear me?
そして、初めての歌枠で歌った、はじめの大好きな歌詞の「ピーターパン」でした。
And that was "Peter Pan," a song with lyrics I love, which I sang in my first karaoke stream.
ありがとうございます！
Thank you very much!
次は、オリ曲を2曲やっていきます！
Next, I'll be performing two original songs!
え？オリ曲2曲？え、そんな持ってたっけ？轟はじめ。
Huh? Two original songs? Did Todoroki Hajime have that many?
「Countach」そして、新曲が出ます！
"Countach" and... a new song is coming out!
2曲続けて聴いてください。それでは聴いてください。
Please listen to these two songs in a row. Here they are.
「Countach」
"Countach"
何のため頑張んの？ 報われない day by day
What am I working for? These unrewarding days, day by day.
結局 正直者が 道化師で踊る残像
In the end, the honest one is just a clown's dancing afterimage.
狡（ずる）く賢く 生きてるあの娘
That girl living so slyly and cleverly...
懐に舞い込む 歌は正義でしょ？
The song that flutters into her pocket is justice, right?
アブラカタブラ 開けるよパンドラ
Abracadabra, I'm opening Pandora's box.
抑えきれないのさ 謳歌（うた）うかサンドラ
I can't hold it back anymore. Shall we celebrate? Sandra.
Shakespeare なる嵐 暴れ馬で食らえカルマ
A Shakespearean storm, take the karma with a wild horse.
Everybody gonna put your hands clap clap まだ見ぬ世界 飛び込め 3 2 1
Everybody gonna put your hands clap clap! Dive into the unknown world! 3, 2, 1...
上がれ 壇上へ 体揺らして
Get up on stage and move your body!
固定概念 あるがままぶち壊せ
Fixed concepts... just smash them as they are!
上がれ 壇上へ 体揺らして
Get up on stage and move your body!
固定概念 あるがままぶち壊せ
Fixed concepts... just smash them as they are!
Countach 最上級の Countach
Countach! The ultimate Countach!
Countach 一身不乱で Countach
Countach! With focused intensity, Countach!
Countach ヒントよこせ Countach
Countach! Give me a hint, Countach!
Countach 何度だって Countach
Countach! Again and again, Countach!
息を潜めて 自分を殺すのはもう慣れてんの
Holding my breath... I'm already used to killing my own self.
存在価値 存在証明なんて どうでもええわ
Value of existence? Proof of existence? I don't give a damn.
宴なら Endless 今宵 突破（トッパ）らうは境界線（ボーダーレス）
If it's a banquet, make it endless. Tonight, we break through the borders.
メシの雷 浴びて暴風 弾け飛んで 劣勢を
Bathed in the lightning of cheers... pop off against the disadvantage!
アブラカタブラ 開けるよパンドラ
Abracadabra, I'm opening Pandora's box.
抑えきれないのさ
I can't hold it back anymore.
バンザイ無能な命に
Banzai for an incompetent life
くだらない欲まがい物だって
Even the silly, fake desires
無理やり飲んで僕はラリアット
Forcing it down, I am a Lariat
偶然愛してるようなもん
It's like I happen to love you
不条理浴びながら僕はハァー
Absorbing absurdity, I...
才能はゼロ
Talent is zero
どうにかしちゃってるキャラ
A character that's somehow messed up
おっがんさいはノー
Oh, that's a no
だってなの
Because...
愛にもたれた言葉で心拍数
My heart rate rises with words leaned on love
生きてくほど胸は沈んでく
The more I live, the more my chest sinks
どうなってんだろうな
I wonder what's going to happen
この音が揺れるの
With this sound shaking
かい摘んでもしょうがねえ
It's no use to summarize it
汗かき稼ぐお金はどんだけ
How much money do I earn sweating?
あーだこーだ
This and that
そんなもんがうるせぇわな
Such things are noisy
バンザイ無能な命に
Banzai for an incompetent life
絡み回ってく脳を満たしてくれ
Fill my brain that's intertwining and spinning
未来予想なんか賭けない
I won't bet on a future forecast
くだらない欲まがい物だってそれ
Even the silly, fake desires, that's it
半端ものなら
If you're a half-baked person...
言えない慣れた
I couldn't say it, I got used to it.
朱色になって
Becoming vermilion,
僕は思い通り
I am just as I wish.
太陽系で足踏まった罵詈雑言インベーダー
Solar system's stomping, abusive invader
足が止まってるシューゲイザー死にそうでもギリですか
Foot-stopped shoegazer, are you barely alive?
のらりくらり交わすわ 初めまして神様
Dodging aimlessly, nice to meet you, God
もし救われるのなら 剥け切るわ今から
If I am to be saved, I'll peel it all off now
got down 揺らぬ got down
Got down, unshakeable got down
飲み込んだ清濁が 君を狂わしてんだ
The purity and corruption I swallowed are driving you mad
待ったもんじゃ届かねえ 汗かき生きと最後も呆けねえ
Waiting won't reach; I'll live sweating and won't be dazed until the end
なんだかんだそんなもんさ 虚しいわな
Anyway, it's just like that; it's empty
バンザイ無能な命に
Banzai for an incompetent life
絡み回ってく脳を満たしてくれ
Fill my brain that's intertwining and spinning
未来予想なんか賭けない
I won't bet on a future forecast
くだらない欲まがい物だってそれ
Even the silly, fake desires, that's it
半端ものなら言えない慣れた
If you're half-baked, I couldn't say it; I got used to it
朱色になって僕は思い通り
Becoming vermilion, I am just as I wish
はじめ！はじめ！エイ！オー！
Hajime! Hajime! Hey! Ho!
レディゴー！
Ready go!
Horns Riot!
One, two, three, four!
はーい！ということで、生誕グッズが出ます！
Alright! So, birthday merch is coming out!
轟はじめ生誕記念2025フルセットは、こんな感じです！
The Todoroki Hajime Birthday Celebration 2025
Full Set looks like this!
ひとつずつ紹介していきます！
I'll introduce them one by one!
ひとつめ、アクリルパネル！Aちさ先生の可愛いイラストと、
First, the acrylic panel!
With a cute illustration by A-chisa-sensei,
オーロラ加工になってます。何やらジャケットを試着しているようで、めちゃめちゃ可愛い！
and an aurora finish. It looks like she's trying
on the jacket, super cute!
ふたつめ、BANCHOアクリルキーホルダー！おもちチャウダー先生のぶんぶんBANCHOのイラストです！
Second, the BANCHO acrylic keychain!
With the Bunbun BANCHO art by Omochi Chowder-sensei!
3つ繋げても、ひとつずつでも使えます。
You can use them linked together or individually.
カラビナは稲妻の形になってます。ぜひカバンとかにつけてみてね！
The carabiner is lightning-shaped.
Please try attaching it to your bag!
3つめ、BANCHOナイロンジャケット！こちらは実際に実物で色味をチェックして使いやすいデザインにしました！
Third, the BANCHO nylon jacket! We checked the
colors with the product for a user-friendly design!
おもちチャウダー先生のミニBANCHOのイラストと、
With the mini-BANCHO art by Omochi Chowder-sensei,
表にははじめの考えたBANCHOのロゴがついてます。
and on the front is the BANCHO logo I came up with.
チャックも稲妻の形になってます。キービジュアルのはじめとお揃いのデザインです！
The zipper is also lightning-shaped.
It's the same design as the one in the key visual!
最後、シチュエーションボイス！ナイロンジャケットにまつわるボイスです。よかったら合わせて聴いてください！
Finally, the situation voice! It's a clip about the
jacket. Please give it a listen!
今回、フルセット購入特典はふたつあります！
There are two bonuses for purchasing the full set!
ひとつめ、直筆サイン入りチェキ風ブロマイドカード！えー、無制限になってます！
First, the hand-signed polaroid-style bromide card!
And it's unlimited!
このライブがよかったなと思ってくださったら、次回以降のライブの励みになるので、ぜひよろしくお願いします！
If you enjoyed this live, it'll encourage me for
future ones, so please check it out!
ふたつめ、オフィシャルショップにて購入した方限定で、hololive OFFICIAL CARD GAMEで使えるカードが1枚つきます！
Second, exclusively at the official shop, you'll get
one hololive OFFICIAL CARD GAME card!
カードの詳細や遊び方については、公式ホームページを見てください！
For details on the card and how to play,
please check the official website!
以上、グッズ紹介でした！言い切ったー！
That's all for the merch intro! I said it all!
あー、まだまだ踊っていくので、ぜひ最後まで見てください！
Ah, I'm going to keep dancing,
so please watch until the end!
そいじゃ、行け！はじめダンスジョイ！
Now then, let's go! Hajime Dance Joy!
エイ！
Hey!
行くぞー！
Let's go!
あー右の皆様こんちはー！
Hello everyone on the right!
はい左の皆様もこんちはー！
And hello everyone on the left!
えー、クラップ！
Alright, clap!
ありがとう！
Thank you!
ありがとー！本当にはじめのライブ来てくれてありがとね！
Thank you! Thanks so much for coming
to Hajime's live!
はい！ということで、皆様本当にありがとうございました！
Alright! So, thank you all so much!
このあと21時、新曲『BANZAI』のMVプレミア公開、そしてグッズ販売も開始されます！
At 21:00, the 'BANZAI' MV will premiere,
and merch sales will also begin!
そして、そのあとはメンバー限定のアンコールライブもあります！
And after that, there's a members-only encore live!
時間ピッタリ！嬉しいー！
Exactly on time! I'm so happy!
あ、トレンドもね、ありがとうございます！本当ーにありがとー！
And the trending topics too, thank you!
Thank you so much!
本当にありがとー！